>> Insertando T_OBRAS_SUBIR.xlsx en T_OBRAS...
   Advertencia: No se pudieron insertar todos los registros. The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.
   ? Error al importar: The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.

>> Insertando T_USUARIOS_SUBIR.xlsx en T_USUARIOS...
   Advertencia: No se pudieron insertar todos los registros. The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.
   ? Error al importar: The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.

>> Insertando T_ANOTACIONES_SUBIR.xlsx en T_ANOTACIONES...
   Advertencia: No se pudieron insertar todos los registros. You must enter a value in the 'T_ANOTACIONES.CodTarea' field.
   ? Error al importar: You must enter a value in the 'T_ANOTACIONES.CodTarea' field.

>> Insertando T_ANOTACIONES_VALID_SUBIR.xlsx en T_ANOTACIONES_VALID...
   Advertencia: No se pudieron insertar todos los registros. You cannot add or change a record because a related record is required in table 'T_ANOTACIONES'.
   ? Error al importar: You cannot add or change a record because a related record is required in table 'T_ANOTACIONES'.
