>> Insertando T_OBRAS_SUBIR.xlsx en T_OBRAS...
   Advertencia: No todos los registros pudieron ser insertados. The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.
   Registros intentados: 52
   Registros insertados: 0
   Registros no insertados: 52

>> Insertando T_USUARIOS_SUBIR.xlsx en T_USUARIOS...
   Advertencia: No todos los registros pudieron ser insertados. The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.
   Registros intentados: 15
   Registros insertados: 0
   Registros no insertados: 15

>> Insertando T_ANOTACIONES_SUBIR.xlsx en T_ANOTACIONES...
   Advertencia: No todos los registros pudieron ser insertados. The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.
   Registros intentados: 38186
   Registros insertados: 0
   Registros no insertados: 38186

>> Insertando T_ANOTACIONES_VALID_SUBIR.xlsx en T_ANOTACIONES_VALID...
   Advertencia: No todos los registros pudieron ser insertados. You cannot add or change a record because a related record is required in table 'T_ANOTACIONES'.
   Registros intentados: 38186
   Registros insertados: 0
   Registros no insertados: 38186
