>> Insertando T_OBRAS_SUBIR.xlsx en T_OBRAS...
   ? Error al importar: The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.

>> Insertando T_USUARIOS_SUBIR.xlsx en T_USUARIOS...
   ? Error al importar: The changes you requested to the table were not successful because they would create duplicate values in the index, primary key, or relationship. Change the data in the field or fields that contain duplicate data, remove the index, or redefine the index to permit duplicate entries and try again.

>> Insertando T_ANOTACIONES_SUBIR.xlsx en T_ANOTACIONES...
   ? Error al importar: Item not found in this collection.

>> Insertando T_ANOTACIONES_VALID_SUBIR.xlsx en T_ANOTACIONES_VALID...
   ? Error al importar: You cannot add or change a record because a related record is required in table 'T_ANOTACIONES'.
